Guide to the Andrew Dickson White papers, 1832-1919.
White, Andrew Dickson papers, 1832-1919
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 5, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Henry T. Allen, December 6, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Elizabeth E. Evans, December 6, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Henry W. Sage, December 6, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 6, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Redfern, December 7, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Wilbur Abbott, December 8, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - C.K. Tuckerman, December 9, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - John Marshall, December 10, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 10, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 10, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - George Lincoln Burr, December 11, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - E.L. Williams, December 11, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    Proceedings. Proceedings of the Board of Trustees
  - Clara White Newberry, December 13, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 13, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - German Printng and Publishing Association, December 14, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - J.McK. Cattell, December 14, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - J.G., December 14, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 14, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    Letter. Addressed to Frederick W. Holls; two pages
  - B. Seeber, December 15, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - The Detroit Tribune, December 15, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Organ of the Columbian Exposition, December 14, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    Dedication Program.
  - Herman Miller, December 15, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Henry T. Allen, December 16, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - W.J. Youmans, December 16, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Archimedes Russell, December 17, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 17, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 17, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Frederick White, December 17, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - T.F. D., December 18, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, December 18, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - R.H. Thurston, December 18, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - O.S. Marden, December 19, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - W.D. Holmes, December 22, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Redfern, December 22, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 22, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Strong White, December 22, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 22, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    Letter. Addressed to P. Bornholdt
  - Willard Fiske, December 25, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Henry T. Allen, December 27, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Clara White Newberry, December 27, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Anne Bruce White, December 27, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Frederick White, December 27, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - N.P. Bornholdt, December 28, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Fletcher Fullard, December 28, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - E. Clarence Hills, December 28, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - N.P. Bornholdt, December 28, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Edward G. Allen, December 29, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Mrs. John Strong Newberry, December 30, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 31, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 31, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to Rev. John F. Mullany
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 31, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to Frederick D. White
  - E. Renault, December 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    Note.
  - Undescribed, December 24, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Undescribed, December 24, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to Dodd, Mead and Company
  - Undescribed, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    Letter. Missing Pages
  - Robert Folger Westcott, January 1, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Undescribed, January 1, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    Notecard.
  - Edward G. Allen, December 31, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - C.H. Crawford, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Undescribed, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Newspaper Clips.
  - Massachusetts General Hopsital, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    .
  - B.F. Stevens, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    . "The Voyage From Lisbon to India"
  - The American Lecturs on the History of Religions, 1894 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - E.G. Allen, January 2, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Wayne MacVeagh, January 2, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Henry T. Allen, January 3, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Frederick White, January 4, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Oscar S. Straus, January 5, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Elizabeth E. Evans, January 6, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Andrew White Newberry, January 6, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Elizabeth E. Evans, January 7, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - George Lincoln Burr, January 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Fletcher Fullard, January 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Robert Stein, January 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Undescribed, December 1894 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    Newspaper Article. "If France and Germany can be reconciled, Universal Peace is in Sight!"
  - Clarence Tucker, January 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - B. W., January 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    Letter. addressed to Frederick White
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, January 9, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 11, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to E.P. Evans; two pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 11, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to Goldwin Smith; two pages
  - H.B. Adams, January 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to Mrs. Tuttle
  - Smithsonian Institution, January 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - L.A. Wait, January 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Alice M. Barnes, January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    Checks. Three checks
  - Clifton R. Breckinridge, January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - George Lincoln Burr, January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - J.McK. Cattell, January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - John Boyd T., January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Strong White, January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Frederick White, January 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - E.P. Evans, January 15, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - L.M. O., January 15, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Tyler M., January 15, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Frederick White, January 15, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Fanny G. Villard, January 15, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 16, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - B.T. Stevens, January 16, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Lucius Warren, January 16, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, January 17, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Undescribed, January 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    Book List.
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    Letter. Addressed to E.P. Evans
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - R.M. Towdeel, January 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - M. R., January 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Alfred Raymond, January 21, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - B.F. Stevens, January 21, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Strong White, January 22, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - B.F. Stevens, January 22, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, January 22, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Fletcher Fullard, January 22, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - John McKibbon, January 24, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - J.P. Langley, January 24, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - N. Howard, January 24, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - B.F. Stevens, January 25, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 25, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Frederick White, January 25, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 26, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - George Lincoln Burr, January 27, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Letter. Two pages; enclosed: letter from W.J. Youmans
  - N.P. Bornholdt, January 28, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 28, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Letter. Addressed to Prof. C.M. Tyler
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 29, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 29, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Sala Filarmonica, January 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Program. "Mattinata Musicale"
  - T.F., January 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - William P. Northrup, January 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Wedding Invitation.
  - Clara White Newberry, January 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Charles S. Francis, January 31, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Letter. Cornell Trip to England Fund
  - O.S. Marden, January 31, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Andrew Dickson White, January 31, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Letter. Addressed to M.C. Tyler; two pages
  - James F., February 2, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Oscar S. Straus, February 4, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Mary McArthur Tuttle, February 4, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Andrew Dickson White, February 5, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Frederick White, February 5, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - C.K. Adams, February 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - E.P. Evans, February 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, February 9, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Frederick White, February 9, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Frederick White, February 10, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    Letter. Addressed to Mrs. White; two pages
  - George Lincoln Burr, February 11, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Fletcher Fullard, February 11, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Undescribed, February 9, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Edward Magill, February 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from Phillip Garrett
  - Andrew Dickson White, February 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Andrew Dickson White, February 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Frederick White, February 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Clarence Tucker, February 13, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Frederick William Holls, February 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - George R. Milliman, February 14, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Lucius Warren, February 15, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - William Channing Russell, February 17, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - W.J. Youmans, February 18, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Willard Fiske, February 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - E.L. Williams, February 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Andrew Dickson White, February 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    Letter. Addressed to Oscar S. Straus
  - L. Bostwick, February 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - J.G. Schurman, February 21, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Andrew Dickson White, February 22, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Baxter & Barnes, February 23, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - George Lincoln Burr, February 23, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - George L.; H. Morse; Moses Coit Burr; Stephens; Tyler, February 1894 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - C. B., February 23, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Ward, February 27, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Fletcher Fullard, February 27, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Clara White Newberry, February 27, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Morill, February 27, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Frederick White, February 28, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Henry T. Allen, March 1, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Thomas A. Jenkins, March 1, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 1, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    Letter. Addressed to Hon. Seth Low
  - The Patria Club, March 2, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    Article.
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 2, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - J.F. Davis, March 3, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 4, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Frederick White, March 5, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Fletcher Fullard, March 6, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 6, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - George Lincoln Burr, March 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - J.G. Schurman, March 8, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    Letter. Letter to graduates of Cornell University
  - B.F. Stevens, March 9, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Walkonsky, March 9, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - S.C. Harris, March 11, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 11, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Frederick White, March 12, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Edward G. Allen, March 13, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Edward G. Allen, March 13, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - B.F. Stevens, March 15, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Louise A. Way, March 16, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - G.W. Smalley, March 17, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - H.L. White, March 17, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Charles S. Francis, March 18, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Willard Fiske, March 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Francis B. Harrison, March 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Magill, March 19, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - George Lincoln Burr, March 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - George Lincoln Burr, March 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - T.F. D., March 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Onondaga Historical Association, March 20, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Henry T. Allen, March 23, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - B.F. Stevens, March 23, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Frederick White, March 23, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Moses Coit Tyler, March 24, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Ricardo Bisecardi, March 25, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Undescribed, March 25, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 25, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Homer B. Sprague, March 26, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 26, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, March 27, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Chiari, March 28, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Willard Fiske, March 29, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - William Channing Russell, March 29, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Undescribed, March 29, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - G. B., March 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Willard Fiske, March 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - J.H. Goar, March 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Undescribed, March 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    Memorandum. Unsigned
  - Andrew Dickson White, March 30, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Willard Fiske, March 31, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Franklin B. Dexter, March 31, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Brown, Shipley & Co., April 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Envelope.
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Frederick White, April 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Shipley & Co., April 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Cook & Son, April 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - J.P. Roosa, April 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Frederick White, April 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 3, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 3, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 3, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Wayne MacVeagh, April 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Letter. Embassy of the United States, Rome
  - Frederick White, April 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Edward L. Nichols, April 5, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - J.P. Roosa, April 5, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - George Lincoln Burr, April 6, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 6, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Letter. Addressed to Clara White Newberry; three pages
  - Frederick White, April 6, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Undescribed, April 7, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - G. B., April 7, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Edward L. Nichols, April 7, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 8, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Willard Fiske, April 9, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - H. Hollingwood, April 9, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Clifton R. Breckinridge, April 8, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 9, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Helen Magill White, April 9, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Chairman of the National University Committee, April 10, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - B.F. Stevens, April 10, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Anna Belden, April 10, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Strong White, April 11, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Frederick White, April 11, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Helen Magill White, April 11, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 12, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - George Lincoln Burr, April 14, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - James Law, April 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 12, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Helen Magill White, April 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Edward L. Nichols, April 14, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - N. R., April 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Charles S. Francis, April 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Frederick White, April 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Langley, April 16, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Invitation. Smithsonian Institution
  - Undescribed, April 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Charles Marseilles, April 19, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Moses Coit Tyler, April 19, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Frederick White, April 19, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - George W. W., April 19, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - E.J. Wheeler, April 20, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - G.W. Smalley, April 22, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 22, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Gertrude Belden, April 23, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - S.S. Eddy, April 23, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - J.G. Cockler, April 23, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Ermano Loescher & Co., April 23, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Willard Fiske, April 24, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Frederick White, April 24, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Theodore Bacon, April 25, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Clara White Newberry, April 25, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Lucius Warren, April 25, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Issac Wayne MacVeagh, April 26, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Moses Coit Tyler, April 26, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Letter. From: M.C. Tyler, J.M. Jenks, G.L. Burr, H.M. Stephens, W.T. Hillcox, C.H. Hull, F. Fetter
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 26, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Dickson White, April 26, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Issac Wayne MacVeagh, April 28, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Brown, Shipley & Co., April 29, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Willard Fiske, April 29, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - B.F. Stevens, April 29, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - B.F. Stevens, May 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Frederick White, May 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Spencer B. Newberry, May 3, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Ernest W. Huffcut, May 3, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - E.G. Allen, May 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Frederick White, May 6, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Henry T. Allen, May 8, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Andrew Strong White, May 8, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Letter. White's nephew
  - George Lincoln Burr, May 5, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Willard Fiske, May 11, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Clarence Tucker, May 11, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Andrew White Newberry, May 12, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Undescribed, May 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - B. Seeber, May 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Letter. Addressed to Henry W. Sage; two pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 14, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Letter. Addressed to Albert Keep
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 14, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Frederick White, May 14, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Letter. Addressed to Francis B. Harrison
  - Andrew Strong White, May 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 16, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 16, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Shipley & Co., May 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Undescribed, May 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, May 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Letter. Addressed to Herbert B. Adams
  - E.P. Evans, May 18, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 18, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Letter. Addressed to Henry C. Potter
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 20, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 20, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - George T. M., May 21, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - George Lincoln Burr, May 22, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Louisa Minturn, May 24, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - B.F. Stevens, May 24, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - E.P. Evans, May 25, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 25, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 25, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    Letter. Addressed to M.C. Tyler; five pages
  - Frederick White, May 25, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - E.P. Evans, May 26, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Helen Magill White, May 27, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Mary P. I., May 28, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Reed, May 28, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Frederick White, May 28, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Clara White Newberry, May 26, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Humphrey B. Chamberlin, May 29, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - W.C. M., May 29, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - C.C. Tiffany, May 29, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Oscar S. Straus, May 31, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, May 31, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Frederick White, May 31, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Robert M. Prince, June 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Dickson White, June 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Helen Magill White, June 1, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    Letter. Eleven pages
  - Lucius Warren, June 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Cox, Sons, Buckley & Co., June 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - T.F. Bayard, June 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - E.L. Williams, June 3, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, June 3, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - St. Paul's Cathedral, June 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    Service Bulletin.
  - Herbert H.D. Peirce, June 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - E.P. Evans, June 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - South Place Ethical Society, June, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    Pamphlet.
  - M.D. Conway, June 2, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Strong White, June 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Andrew Strong White, June 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - M.F. Berry, June 5, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - M.D. Conway, June 5, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Stanley Gibbons, June 5, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Allen, June 5, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - E.G. Allen, June 4, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - George P. Fisher, June 7, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Undescribed, June 7, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Letter. Addressed to Fred
  - Wolkenstein, June 7, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Theodore Merle, June 8, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - H.B. Adams, June 10, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - John Henry Barron, June 11, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - E.G. Allen, June 12, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Yale College, June 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Clara White Newberry, June 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Horace K. White, June 13, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Theodore Bacon, June 14, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Spencer B. Newberry, June 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - M. Samuel, June 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Oscar S. Straus, June 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Clarence Tucker, June 15, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Andrew White Newberry, June 16, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Robert Stein, June 16, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    Letter. Enclosed: National Union For Practical Progress circular
  - J. Edwards Clarke, June 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Ellen E. Dickinson, June 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - J.M. Magill, June 17, 1895 (Box 72, Folder 11)